{"data":[{"question":"There is no water _____ that island","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"Look! There's a cat _____ the roof.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"When the weather is nice Mrs Bruckner sits ____ her balcony.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"Please serve the souffl\u00e9 _____ once.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"Are you going away ____ Easter.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"We saw a ballet _____ Julia's birthday.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"We assign our employees new tasks _____ a weekly basis.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- We often say \" in newspaper\"","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"Put the rubbish _____ the bin.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n \n- At work: a place where you do your job, which is not your home","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"Horses were the principal means of transportation _____ nineteenth century.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"The plane is due to arrive ______ 19.25","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"}]}